question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The name of the main character of the video game The Legend of Zelda, is Zelda.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {
        "category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The Pythagorean theorem states that the square of the hypotenuse is equal to the product of the squares of the other two sides.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004 The Aviator.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet in both of the movies Interstellar and The Martian.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Comics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "In the comic book Archie, Betty is friends with Veronica because she is rich.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "It is automatically considered entrapment in the United States if the police sell you illegal substances without revealing themselves.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The longest place named in the United States is Lake Chargoggagoggmanchauggagoggchaubunagungamaugg, located near Webster, MA.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Books", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The book 1984 was published in 1949.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "In the game Melty Blood Actress Again Current Code, you can enter Blood Heat mode in Half Moon style.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "It was once believed that injecting shark cartilage into people would prevent them from contracting cancer.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Donkey Kong was originally set to be a Popeye arcade game.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Bill Cipher in the show Gravity Falls is the good guy.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together to archive every tweet by American citizens.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The open source program Redis is a relational database server.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Samuel L. Jackson had the words, &#039;Bad Motherf*cker&#039; in-scripted on his lightsaber during the filming of Star Wars.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The Sniper SMG in Team Fortress 2, was originally intended to be the Scout primary weapon.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "TF2: Sentry rocket damage falloff is calculated based on the distance between the sentry and the enemy, not the engineer and the enemy", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Toronto is the capital city of the North American country of Canada.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Antarctica is the largest desert in the world.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In the Toaru Kagaku no Railgun anime,  espers can only reach a maximum of level 6 in their abilities.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The NVidia GTX 1080 gets its name because it can only render at a 1920x1080 screen resolution.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "A Saxophone is a brass instrument.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "California is larger than Japan.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Bulbasaur is the only starter pokemon that is a Grass\/Poison type.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Stevie Wonder real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In Riot Games League of Legends the name of Halloween event is called The Reckoning.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In Battlestar Galactica (2004), Cylons were created by man as cybernetic workers and soldiers.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Norway has a larger land area than Sweden.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Watch_Dogs 2 is a prequel.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Klingons express emotion in art through opera and poetry.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Resident Evil 4 was originally meant to be a Nintendo GameCube exclusive.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Board Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The board game Go has more possible legal positions than the number of atoms in the visible universe.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Sports", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In Rugby League, performing a 40-20 is punished by a free kick for the opposing team.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "An average human can go two weeks without water.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In Doctor Who, the Doctor gets his TARDIS by stealing it.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Nick Mason is the only member to appear on every Pink Floyd album.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered in 1983 inside swimming pools and drinking water.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The character that would eventually become Dr. Eggman was considered for the role of Sega new flagship mascot before Sonic was.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Michael Jackson wrote The Simpsons song Do the Bartman.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "An episode of The Simpsons is dedicated to Moe Szyslak bar rag.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The 2011 movie The Adventures of Tintin was directed by Steven Spielberg.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Tigers have one colour of skin despite the stripey fur.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "An isosceles triangle has two sides of equal length as opposed to three.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Francis Bacon died from a fatal case of pneumonia while he was attempting to preserve meat by stuffing a chicken with snow.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The pickled gherkin was first added to hamburgers because a US health law required all fast-food to include a source of Vitamin C.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "John Williams composed the music for Star Wars.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The Simpsons family is named after creator Matt Groening real family.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Musicals & Theatres", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The protagonist names in &#039;Who Afraid of Virginia Woolf&#039;, George and Martha, were derived from George Washington and his wife.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
